groupbox.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy policy

**Groupbox Principles**  
We built the Groupbox website to make it easy to keep up to date with your friends. We encourage you to use Groupbox to share your personal information - with that, we know that you don't want all of your personal information shared with the wider world.  That is why we give you control of your information. Our default privacy settings limit the information displayed in your profile to your friends (those people you have nominated to be your friends).   
   
Groupbox follows three core principles:   
   
**1\. You should have control over your personal information.**  

Groupbox helps you share information with your friends and people around you. You choose what information you put in your profile, including contact and personal information, pictures, interests and groups you join. And you control with whom you share that information through the privacy settings on your profile and settings pages.   

**2\. You should have access to the information others want to share.**

There is an ever increasing world of information on the Internet and Groupbox allows you to easily view that which is relevant to you.   

**3\. You should be protected from those that do not wish to follow the rules.** Groupbox runs on the input of users and thus we value that input above anything else.   

Sharing information should be easy. And we want to provide you with the privacy tools necessary to control how and with whom you share that information. If you have questions or ideas, please [contact Groupbox](http://groupbox.com/Contact.aspx)  

**Using Groupbox Safely**  
For information for users and parents about staying safe on Groupbox please contact us.   
   
**Use of information**  
  
Groupbox's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using Groupbox located at www.groupbox.com ("Groupbox" or "Web Site"). 

By using or accessing Groupbox, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our privacy staff [contact Groupbox](http://groupbox.com/Contact.aspx). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe Watchdog at [ http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.   

**Information we collect**  
  
When you visit Groupbox you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.   

You post User Content (as defined in the Groupbox [Terms of use](http://groupbox.com/Terms.aspx)[](http://groupbox.com/terms.php)) on the Site at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.   

**Links**  
Groupbox may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Groupbox.
